[{"answer": "It's also miraculous that our tent didn't just fly away.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "You OK?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "Beauty.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "What do you think when you see this photo?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "Smiling all the time.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "What was she like in high school?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "Oh, full heart, my whole heart and soul.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "How did Krystle make you feel?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "AMPBELL: Smart.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "What kind of young woman did she become?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "Oh, lots of friends.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "Lots of friends?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "Oh, everything.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "What did that mean to you?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "I wish I could go up and grab her and kiss her.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "What do you think when you see her there?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "I don't.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "How do you make sense of this?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "You can't believe something that something like this would happen to someone you love?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "Martin was a great kid.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "And what do you know about the condition, first of all, of poor Martin's mother and his sister?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "I haven't heard.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "Do you know any more about their condition?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "I had seen from another good friend of mine that she had called me and told me.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "Caitlin, how did you hear about what had happened?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "Yes, the Richard family all around, from Denise to the father, Bill to Henry, Martin and Jane, they were always just so welcoming and kind, and I really enjoyed babysitting for them.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "Is that your take on the Richard family?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "The vigil was amazing.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "What was the vigil like?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "Well, at this point, we are told this is according to the Senate sergeant in arms, Terry Gainor, that the envelope did test positive today at the actual lab, Piers.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "What do we know?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "That's a great question.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "Or has that already been ruled out?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "Well, I really do think we have to be patient and wait and see.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "What is your take on where this investigation may be going?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "We had a initial briefing tonight by the director of the FBI as well as Secretary Napolitano and the director of the NSA.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "Have you got any inside-track intelligence whatsoever that would hint at either of those two strands?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "Well, I certainly wouldn't do that.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "Is there any realistic criticism that should be leveled to anyone here?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "CHIFF: Well, I think it is -- I think it's very smart of them.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "What is your view of that?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "Well, honestly, Piers, I'm not sure that we know that.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "From everything that you've seen and read, do you see real signs that this is more likely to be some form of domestic extremist attack?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "Well, there are a couple of observations I have, Piers.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "From what you've seen and read, where is your head going with this?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "No, I can't see them.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "Can you see these pictures, Bob?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "Piers, what I would say is actually I think the answer is something a little bit in the middle of your -- Bob Baer and Mark, what they're saying to you.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "What do you make of the way the investigation is unfurling here?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "Well, I think in general, it's more likely to be a lone wolf.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "Mark Potok, if it is a domestic terror attack, is it more likely, from your experience, to be a lone wolf or part of an existing group?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "Well, the Chinese have been the victims of al Qaeda in the weaker part of the country.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "What would be the repercussions if, for argument's sake, it does turn out to be some sort of al Qaeda related attack in terms of the impact on countries like China who have been affected?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, I think that when I wrote that, I probably was a little more despondent than I should've been.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "Is that, do you think, how most people in Boston feel today?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "Determination not to change our lifestyle, not to make -- not to give in to the intimidation that is at the heart of all terrorist acts.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "Is it one of not just resolution, but determination not to be beaten?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Well, we were not going to cancel our wedding, but we did think about possibly postponing it or coming up with alternative plans.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "But once you realized what had happened, did you have any second thoughts, any doubts that you should go through with it?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "Robert, obviously when you realized the scale of what had happened, after horror and devastation everywhere, did that make you even more determined to go through this, as Kelli said, to make sure the terrorist didn't win?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "Right now, you can't make sense of it.", "docId": "130416pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "What do you make of the people or the person that did this?", "qSentId": 554}]